Dmytro Hrybinnykov

JavaScript/Flutter Developer Born 1990 in Kharkiv, Ukraine





+48 886 356 729

About me

I have a diverse experience as a Software Developer since the start of my career in 2014. Mostly, there were Frontend positions (React and Flutter). However, I'm familiar with the Backend technologies as well (Node.js and PHP). I have a stong knowledge of JavaScript and Dart languages, and I'm always open to learn new technologies. Also, I have experience in setup CI/CD pipelines for mobile and web apps, integration with 3rd party services (payment gateways, social networks, etc.).

Skills



Languages

English - B2 (Upper-Intermediate)

Education

Master's Degree O.M. Beketov National University of Urban Economy in Kharkiv. Industrial and civil

Experience

Freelance

Frontend developer

Jan 2023 - Present

Freelance projects mostly with Flutter or React stack. Implemented new features and fixed existing bugs.

Tech stack: Flutter, Freezed, Drift SQL, Bloc, React, Redux, RTKQuery, Next.js, Node.js, Prisma orm, Tailwind css, Material UI

Yojji Itd.

Flutter developer (different projects)

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

Flutter projects which consisted of bug fixing and small features implementation. In most cases with farebase backend

Flutter developer (MVP app in healthcare)

Nov 2021 - Aug 2022

Developed MVP app for communication between patients and caregivers. Tech stack: Flutter, Bloc, Firebase, Freezed, Dio, Retrofit, Codemagic

Flutter developer (app for timepiece collectors)

Oct 2020 - Nov 2021

Planned project architecture, converted requirements into user stories. Integrated 3rd-party services, such as PayPal, Apple Pay, Docusign. Delegated features development to team members. Implemented features for mobile and backend part. Made code reviews. Mentored colleagues who came into Flutter from JS/React native

Tech stack: Flutter, flutter_redux, dio, retrofit, Stripe, PayPal, Getx, Apple pay, Bitrise, Docusign, Nest.js, Node.js

Flutter developer (app for photographers)

May 2020 - Oct 2020

Developed application from scratch, investigated Flutter architecture approaches, communicated with designer to improve UI & UX, prioritize tasks & features to make MVP.

Eastern Peak

JS developer (Bizzabo.com)

Jan 2017 - May 2020

Developed new features with React. is stack, planned features, code reviews, etc. Covered existing code with unit and automation tests. Supported and refactored existing codebase.

Tech stack: React, Redux, Redux-forms, Next.is, Material UI, Node.is, Git, Kubernetes, Nightwatch.is, Circleci

Devico Solutions

JS/PHP developer (CRM system for dental lab)

Jan 2016 - Jan 2017

Developed new features. Participated in features planning, code reviews, etc. Tech stack: React, Redux, Bootstrap, PHP, Zend framework 2, MySQL, Doctrine ORM

PHP/JS developer (Financial advisor system)

Nov 2014 - Jan 2016

Reverse engineered existing Delphi app and implemented the same business logic in web application. Developed new features, participated in new features planning, code reviews, etc.

Tech stack: ¡Query, Coffeescript, PHP, Zend framework 2, MySQL, Doctrine ORM, Bootstrap